Guide to the Walt Horan Papers 1939-1967
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 5: Subject files, 1943-1964
  - Customs
    - 1946-1947 (Box 221, Folder 5451)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 221, Folder 5452)
    - 1962 (Box 221, Folder 5453)
    - 1961 (Box 221, Folder 5454)
    - 1960 (Box 221, Folder 5455)
    - 1958 (Box 221, Folder 5456-5457)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 221, Folder 5458)
    - 1956 (Box 221, Folder 5459)
    - 1955 (Box 221, Folder 5460)
    - 1954 (Box 221, Folder 5461)
    - 1953 (Box 221, Folder 5462)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 221, Folder 5463)
    - 1949-1952 (Box 221, Folder 5464)
  - Dairy: Oleomargarine
    - 1943-1945 (Box 222, Folder 5465)
    - 1962 (Box 222, Folder 5466)
  - Employment, Government
    - 1956 (Box 222, Folder 5467-5468)
    - 1955 (Box 222, Folder 5469-5470)
    - 1952 (Box 222, Folder 5471-5473)
    - 1951 (Box 222, Folder 5474-5478)
    - 1950 (Box 222, Folder 5479-5481)
    - 1950 (continued) (Box 223, Folder 5482-5483)
    - 1949 (Box 223, Folder 5484-5486)
    - 1964 (Box 223, Folder 5487-5488)
    - 1963 (Box 223, Folder 5489-5491)
    - 1962 (Box 223, Folder 5492-5493)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 223, Folder 5494)
    - 1961 (Box 223, Folder 5495-5499)
    - 1960 (Box 223, Folder 5500-5501)
    - 1959 (Box 224, Folder 5502-5508)
    - 1960 (Box 224, Folder 5509-5510)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 224, Folder 5511)
    - 1958 (Box 224, Folder 5512)
    - 1957 (Box 224, Folder 5513-5514)
    - 1956 (Box 224, Folder 5515)
    - 1955 (Box 224, Folder 5516-5517)
    - 1954 (Box 224, Folder 5518)
    - 1953 (Box 224, Folder 5519)
    - 1954 (Box 224, Folder 5520)
    - 1954 (continued) (Box 225, Folder 5521-5523)
    - 1953 (Box 225, Folder 5524-5526)
    - 1948 (Box 225, Folder 5527-5529)
    - 1947 (Box 225, Folder 5530-5532)
    - 1946 (Box 225, Folder 5533)
    - 1947 (Box 225, Folder 5534-5535)
  - Equal Rights for Women
    - 1950-1956 (Box 225, Folder 5536)
    - 1948-1950 (Box 225, Folder 5537)
    - 1947 (Box 225, Folder 5538)
  - Flood
    - 1944 (Box 226, Folder 5539)
    - 1948 (Box 226, Folder 5540-5550)
    - 1949 (Box 226, Folder 5551-5552)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 226, Folder 5553)
    - 1950 (Box 226, Folder 5554)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 227, Folder 5555)
    - 1950 (Box 227, Folder 5556)
    - 1951 (Box 227, Folder 5557-5561)
    - 1952 (Box 227, Folder 5562)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 227, Folder 5563)
    - 1953 (Box 227, Folder 5564)
    - 1953-1957 (Box 227, Folder 5565)
    - 1957 (Box 227, Folder 5566)
  - Foreign Aid
    - 1949 (Box 227, Folder 5567-5570)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 228, Folder 5571)
    - 1950 (Box 228, Folder 5572-5574)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 228, Folder 5575-5576)
    - 1951 (Box 228, Folder 5577-5578)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 228, Folder 5579)
    - 1952 (Box 228, Folder 5580-5583)
    - 1951-1957 (Box 228, Folder 5584)
    - 1957 (Box 228, Folder 5585)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 228, Folder 5586)
    - 1958 (Box 228, Folder 5587)
    - 1946 (Box 228, Folder 5588-5591)
    - 1946 (continued) (Box 229, Folder 5592)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 229, Folder 5593)
    - 1947 (Box 229, Folder 5594)
    - 1948 (Box 229, Folder 5595-5602)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 229, Folder 5603)
    - 1947 (Box 229, Folder 5604-5605)
    - 1961 (Box 229, Folder 5606-5611)
    - 1961(continued) (Box 230, Folder 5612-5614)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 230, Folder 5615)
    - 1960 (Box 230, Folder 5616-5617)
    - 1959 (Box 230, Folder 5618)
    - 1964 (Box 230, Folder 5619-5621)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 230, Folder 5622)
    - 1963 (Box 230, Folder 5623-5624)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 230, Folder 5625)
    - 1962-1964 (Box 230, Folder 5626)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 230, Folder 5627)
    - 1962 (Box 230, Folder 5628)
    - 1962 (continued) (Box 231, Folder 5629-5632)
  - Fruit and Vegetables
    - 1964 (Box 231, Folder 5633)
    - 1959-1964 (Box 231, Folder 5634)
    - 1959 (Box 231, Folder 5635)
    - 1958 (Box 231, Folder 5636)
    - 1955-1958 (Box 231, Folder 5637)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 231, Folder 5638)
    - 1948 (Box 231, Folder 5639-5640)
    - 1947 (Box 231, Folder 5641)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 231, Folder 5642)
    - 1961 (Box 231, Folder 5643)
    - 1943 (Box 231, Folder 5644)
    - 1944 (Box 231, Folder 5645-5646)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 231, Folder 5647)
    - 1943 (Box 232, Folder 5648)
    - 1952 (Box 232, Folder 5649)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 232, Folder 5650)
    - 1945-1950 (Box 232, Folder 5651)
    - 1947 (Box 232, Folder 5652)
    - 1958-1961 (Box 232, Folder 5653)
    - 1958 (Box 232, Folder 5654)
    - 1960 (Box 232, Folder 5655-5657)
  - Fertilizers, 1947-1949 (Box 232, Folder 5658)
  - Fish and Wildlife
    - 1963-1964 (Box 232, Folder 5659)
    - 1962 (Box 232, Folder 5660)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 232, Folder 5661)
    - 1961 (Box 232, Folder 5662-5663)
    - 1960 (Box 232, Folder 5664)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 232, Folder 5665)
    - 1959 (Box 232, Folder 5666-5667)
    - 1957 (Box 232, Folder 5668-5669)
    - 1957 (continued) (Box 233, Folder 5670)
    - 1955-1957 (Box 233, Folder 5671)
    - 1955 (Box 233, Folder 5672)
    - 1954 (Box 233, Folder 5673)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 233, Folder 5674)
    - 1950-1952 (Box 233, Folder 5675)
    - 1950 (Box 233, Folder 5676)
    - 1949 (Box 233, Folder 5677)
    - 1948 (Box 233, Folder 5678)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 233, Folder 5679)
    - 1947 (Box 233, Folder 5680-5682)
  - Commercial Fishing
    - 1963-1964 (Box 233, Folder 5683)
    - 1961-1963 (Box 233, Folder 5684)
    - 1958-1960 (Box 233, Folder 5685)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 233, Folder 5686)
    - 1957 (Box 233, Folder 5687)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 233, Folder 5688)
    - 1954 (Box 233, Folder 5689)
    - 1953 (Box 233, Folder 5690)
    - 1951-1953 (Box 233, Folder 5691)
    - 1951 (Box 233, Folder 5692)
    - 1950 (Box 233, Folder 5693)
    - 1950 (continued) (Box 234, Folder 5694)
    - 1949 (Box 234, Folder 5695-5696)
    - 1947 (Box 234, Folder 5697-5698)
    - 1948 (Box 234, Folder 5699-5700)
    - 1945 (Box 234, Folder 5701)
    - 1944 (Box 234, Folder 5702-5703)
    - 1943 (Box 234, Folder 5704-5705)
  - Gas and Oil
    - 1958-1960 (Box 234, Folder 5706)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 234, Folder 5707)
    - 1954-1957 (Box 234, Folder 5708)
    - 1953-1955 (Box 234, Folder 5709)
    - 1953 (Box 234, Folder 5710-5711)
    - 1952 (Box 234, Folder 5712)
    - 1951 (Box 234, Folder 5713)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 234, Folder 5714)
    - 1953 (Box 235, Folder 5715)
    - 1952 (Box 235, Folder 5716)
    - 1951 (Box 235, Folder 5717)
    - 1948-1951 (Box 235, Folder 5718)
    - 1943-1948 (Box 235, Folder 5719)
  - Grange
    - 1954 (Box 235, Folder 5720-5721)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 235, Folder 5722)
    - 1953 (Box 235, Folder 5723)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 235, Folder 5724)
    - 1951 (Box 235, Folder 5725)
    - 1950 (Box 235, Folder 5726)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 235, Folder 5727)
    - 1945-1947 (Box 235, Folder 5728)
    - 1945 (Box 235, Folder 5729-5730)
    - 1944 (Box 235, Folder 5731)
    - 1943 (Box 235, Folder 5732)
    - 1943 (continued) (Box 236, Folder 5733)
    - 1964 (Box 236, Folder 5734)
    - 1963 (Box 236, Folder 5735)
    - 1961 (Box 236, Folder 5736)
    - 1962 (Box 236, Folder 5737)
    - 1961 (Box 236, Folder 5738)
    - 1960 (Box 236, Folder 5739)
    - 1959 (Box 236, Folder 5740)
    - 1958 (Box 236, Folder 5741-5742)
    - 1957 (Box 236, Folder 5743-5747)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 236, Folder 5748)
  - Highways
    - 1955 (Box 237, Folder 5749-5754)
    - 1954 (Box 237, Folder 5755-5756)
    - 1951-1954 (Box 237, Folder 5757)
    - 1947-1949 (Box 237, Folder 5758)
    - 1948 (Box 237, Folder 5759)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 237, Folder 5760)
    - 1949 (Box 237, Folder 5761-5763)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 237, Folder 5764-5765)
    - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 5766)
    - 1948-1950 (Box 237, Folder 5767)
    - 1950 (Box 237, Folder 5768)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 238, Folder 5769)
    - 1949-1951 (Box 238, Folder 5770)
    - 1951 (Box 238, Folder 5771-5774)
    - 1949-1952 (Box 238, Folder 5775)
    - 1952 (Box 238, Folder 5776-5778)
    - 1950-1952 (Box 238, Folder 5779)
    - 1949 (Box 238, Folder 5780)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 238, Folder 5781)
    - 1948 (Box 238, Folder 5782)
    - 1947 (Box 238, Folder 5783)
    - 1945 (Box 238, Folder 5784)
    - 1949 (Box 238, Folder 5785)
    - 1943 (Box 238, Folder 5786-5787)
    - 1944 (Box 238, Folder 5788-5789)
    - 1944 (Box 239, Folder 5790-5792)
    - 1955 (Box 239, Folder 5793-5797)
    - 1959 (Box 239, Folder 5798-5802)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 239, Folder 5803)
    - 1958 (Box 239, Folder 5804-5805)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 239, Folder 5806)
    - 1957 (Box 239, Folder 5807-5808)
    - 1956 (Box 239, Folder 5809)
    - 1956 (continued) (Box 240, Folder 5810-5816)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 240, Folder 5817)
    - 1964 (Box 240, Folder 5818)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 240, Folder 5819)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 240, Folder 5820)
    - 1959 (Box 240, Folder 5821)
    - 1963 (Box 240, Folder 5822-5823)
    - 1962 (Box 240, Folder 5824)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 240, Folder 5825)
    - 1961 (Box 240, Folder 5826-5828)
    - 1960 (Box 240, Folder 5829-5832)
  - Housing
    - 1947 (Box 241, Folder 5833-5835)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 241, Folder 5836-5837)
    - 1946 (Box 241, Folder 5838-5840)
    - 1944 (Box 241, Folder 5841)
    - 1944-1955 (Box 241, Folder 5842)
    - 1945 (Box 241, Folder 5843)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 241, Folder 5844)
    - 1944 (Box 241, Folder 5845-5847)
    - 1943 (Box 241, Folder 5848)
    - 1949 (Box 242, Folder 5849-5855)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 242, Folder 5856)
    - 1948 (Box 242, Folder 5857-5864)
    - 1947 (Box 242, Folder 5865-5866)
    - 1947, 1952-1953 (Box 242, Folder 5867)
    - 1952 (Box 242, Folder 5868)
    - 1951 (Box 242, Folder 5869)
    - 1951 (continued) (Box 243, Folder 5870)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 243, Folder 5871)
    - 1952 (Box 243, Folder 5872-5875)
    - 1951 (Box 243, Folder 5876)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 243, Folder 5877)
    - 1951 (Box 243, Folder 5878-5879)
    - 1950 (Box 243, Folder 5880-5884)
    - 1957 (Box 243, Folder 5885)
    - 1956 (Box 243, Folder 5886-5888)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 243, Folder 5889)
    - 1954 (Box 244, Folder 5890-5891)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 244, Folder 5892)
    - 1953 (Box 244, Folder 5893-5895)
    - 1953-1955 (Box 244, Folder 5896)
    - 1955 (Box 244, Folder 5897-5900)
    - 1964 (Box 244, Folder 5901)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 244, Folder 5902)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 244, Folder 5903)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 244, Folder 5904)
    - 1961 (Box 244, Folder 5905-5906)
    - 1960 (Box 244, Folder 5907)
    - 1959 (Box 244, Folder 5908-5909)
    - 1959 (continued) (Box 245, Folder 5910-5911)
    - 1958 (Box 245, Folder 5912-5915)
    - 1957 (Box 245, Folder 5916)
    - 1957-1960 (Box 245, Folder 5917)
    - 1957 (Box 245, Folder 5918-5921)
  - Immigration
    - 1943 (Box 245, Folder 5922-5923)
    - 1944-1947 (Box 245, Folder 5924)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 245, Folder 5925)
    - 1947 (Box 245, Folder 5926)
    - 1948 (Box 245, Folder 5927-5928)
    - 1949-1951 (Box 245, Folder 5929-5930)
    - 1949 (Box 245, Folder 5931)
    - 1950 (Box 245, Folder 5932)
    - 1949 (Box 245, Folder 5933)
    - 1950 (Box 246, Folder 5934)
    - 1951 (Box 246, Folder 5935-5937)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 246, Folder 5938)
    - 1951 (Box 246, Folder 5939-5940)
    - 1952 (Box 246, Folder 5941-5942)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 246, Folder 5943)
    - 1950-1952 (Box 246, Folder 5944)
    - 1949, 1957 (Box 246, Folder 5945)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 246, Folder 5946)
    - 1958 (Box 246, Folder 5947)
    - 1957 (Box 246, Folder 5948-5951)
    - 1956 (Box 246, Folder 5952-5953)
    - 1955 (Box 246, Folder 5954-5955)
    - 1954 (Box 246, Folder 5956-5957)
    - 1953 (Box 246, Folder 5958)
    - 1953 (continued) (Box 247, Folder 5959-5960)
    - 1953-1960 (Box 247, Folder 5961)
    - 1960 (Box 247, Folder 5962)
    - 1964 (Box 247, Folder 5963)
    - 1956 (Box 247, Folder 5964)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 247, Folder 5965)
    - 1963 (Box 247, Folder 5966)
    - 1960-1962 (Box 247, Folder 5967)
    - 1961 (Box 247, Folder 5968)
    - 1964 (Box 247, Folder 5969-5970)
    - 1963 (Box 247, Folder 5971)
    - 1961 (Box 247, Folder 5972)
    - 1961-192 (Box 247, Folder 5973)
    - 1962 (Box 247, Folder 5974-5975)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 247, Folder 5976-5977)
    - 1961 (Box 247, Folder 5978)
    - 1959 (Box 247, Folder 5979-5980)
    - 1959 (Box 247, Folder 5980)
  - Indians
    - 1947 (major subjects: Chief Joseph, Education, Colville Tribe, Legislation) (Box 248, Folder 5981-5987)
    - 1942-1947 (major subjects: Colville Indians: Budget, Business Council, Mundt Resolution, Paschal Sherman) (Box 248, Folder 5988-5997)
    - 1948-1949 (major subjects: Indian Bureau, Mescapero Apache Tribe, Indian Liquor Law, Education, Quinault Indian Reservation, Timber, Constitution and bylaws of the Affiliated Tribes of Northwest Indians, Indian appropriations) (Box 248, Folder 5998-5999)
    - 1948-1949 (continued) (Box 249, Folder 6000-6011)
    - Treaty with Colville Indians, 1905 (reproduction) (Box 249, Folder 6012)
    - 1953-1956 (major subject: Minerals and Miners) (Box 249, Folder 6013-6015)
    - 1960, 1963 (major subject: Chief Joseph) (Box 249, Folder 6016-6018)
    - 1948-1952 (major subjects: Kuehne Land Sale, Governors Interstate Indian Council, Patents, Tribal Enrollment, Frank George, Bureau of Indian Affairs, Colville Business Council) (Box 249, Folder 6019-6020)
    - 1948-1952 (continued) (Box 250, Folder 6021-6032)
    - 1954 (major subjects: Power Lines, Mining, Indian Allotment) (Box 250, Folder 6033-6039)
    - 1953 (major subjects: Colville Tribal Council, Timber, Colville Indian Agency) (Box 251, Folder 6040-6052)
    - 1950-1951 (major subjects: Hospital and Medical Services, President Truman visit to Grand Coulee Dam) (Box 251, Folder 6053-6058)
    - 1954-1956 (major subjects: Colville Restoration Bill, Coeur d'Alene Tribal Council, H.R. 7190. H.R. 6154, Termination of Federal Supervision) (Box 252, Folder 6059-6074)
    - 1956 (major subjects: H.R.'s 9505, 9487, 8484, 8347, 8325, 7190, 6154; Bureau of Indian Affairs) (Box 253, Folder 6078-6082)
    - 1955-1956 (major subjects: Chief Joseph, Realty Branch of Colville Agency, Jim Jones, Cleveland Kamiakin, Bureau of Indian Affairs, Mining Claims, Spokane Indian Reservation, Eastern Washington Conference on Indian Affairs) (Box 253, Folder 6083-6092)
    - 1949 (major subject: Justification for Restoration "Opened" Lands Diminished Portion Reservation) (Box 253, Folder 6093)
    - 1958-1960 (major subjects: Mineral Rights, Makah Tribe, Monse Irrigation Project, S. 56, H.R. 8224, Land Leases, Hospitals) (Box 253, Folder 6094-6096)
    - 1958-1960 (continued) (Box 254, Folder 6097-6101)
    - 1956-1958 (major subjects: Yellowtail Dam and Reservoir, Allotments, H.R. 3771, Forest Management Report) (Box 254, Folder 6102-6107)
    - 1957-1961 (major subjects: Chief Joseph, H.R. 2839. H.R. 11599, H.R. 6560, Secretary's Task Force on Indian Affairs, S. 3510, S, 3312, Mining and Mineral Rights) (Box 254, Folder 6108-6112)
    - 1957-1961 (continued) (Box 255, Folder 6113-6124)
    - 1959-1964 (major subjects: Grand Coulee Dam Reservoir and Indian Zone, Indian Health, various reports) (Box 255, Folder 6125-6129)
    - 1962-1964 (major subjects: Monse Irrigation Project, Population, Art Exhibition: Portraits of Nez Perce Indians, Bureau of Indian Affairs, Timber Management) (Box 256, Folder 6130-6141)
    - 1962 (major subject: Legislation) (Box 256, Folder 6142-6148)
  - Industries: Pacific Northwest
    - 1951-1952 (Box 257, Folder 6149)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 257, Folder 6150)
    - 1948-1950 (Box 257, Folder 6151)
    - 1947 (Box 257, Folder 6152)
    - 1945-1947 (Box 257, Folder 6153)
    - 1945 (Box 257, Folder 6154-6155)
    - 1947 (Box 257, Folder 6156-6159)
    - 1962-1964 (Box 257, Folder 6160)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 257, Folder 6161)
    - 1963 (Box 257, Folder 6162)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 257, Folder 6163)
    - 1959-1961 (Box 257, Folder 6164)
    - 1959 (Box 257, Folder 6165)
    - 1948 (Box 257, Folder 6166-6169)
    - 1962 (Box 257, Folder 6170)
    - 1962 (continued) (Box 258, Folder 6171)
    - 1947 (Box 258, Folder 6172)
    - 1948-1953 (Box 258, Folder 6173)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 258, Folder 6174)
    - 1941-1943 (Box 258, Folder 6175)
    - 1942 (Box 258, Folder 6176)
    - 1943 (Box 258, Folder 6177)
    - 1942 (Box 258, Folder 6178)
    - 1943 (Box 258, Folder 6179-6181)
    - 1943-1945 (Box 258, Folder 6182)
  - Insurance and Banking
    - 1961-1963 (Box 258, Folder 6183)
    - 1943 (Box 258, Folder 6184-6186)
  - Irrigation and Reclamation
    - 1945-1946 (Box 258, Folder 6187)
    - 1945 (Box 258, Folder 6188-6192)
    - 1945 (continued) (Box 259, Folder 6193-6195)
    - 1944 (Box 259, Folder 6196-6199)
    - 1943 (Box 259, Folder 6200)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 259, Folder 6201)
    - 1944 (Box 259, Folder 6202)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 259, Folder 6203)
    - 1961-1964 (Box 259, Folder 6204)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 259, Folder 6205)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 259, Folder 6206)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 259, Folder 6207)
    - 1957-1959 (Box 259, Folder 6208)
    - 1953-1955 (Box 259, Folder 6209)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 259, Folder 6210)
    - 1951 (Box 259, Folder 6211)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 260, Folder 6212)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 260, Folder 6213)
    - 1948 (Box 260, Folder 6214)
    - 1947 (Box 260, Folder 6215-6216)
    - 1945 (Box 260, Folder 6217)
    - 1947 (Box 260, Folder 6218-6232)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 260, Folder 6233-6234)
    - 1947 (Box 260, Folder 6235-6237)
    - 1947 (continued) (Box 261, Folder 6238)
    - 1948 (Box 261, Folder 6239-6244)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 261, Folder 6245)
    - 1947 (Box 261, Folder 6246-6257)
    - 1949 (Box 262, Folder 6258-6260)
    - 1948 (Box 262, Folder 6261-6273)
    - 1949 (Box 262, Folder 6274)
    - 1949 (continued) (Box 263, Folder 6275-6293)
    - 1951 (Box 264, Folder 6294-6295)
    - 1950 (Box 264, Folder 6296-6300)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 264, Folder 6301)
    - 1950 (Box 264, Folder 6302-6303)
    - 1949 (Box 264, Folder 6304)
    - 1950 (Box 264, Folder 6305)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 264, Folder 6306)
    - 1950 (Box 264, Folder 6307-6311)
    - 1950 (continued) (Box 265, Folder 6312-6325)
    - 1950-51 (Box 265, Folder 6326)
    - 1951 (Box 265, Folder 6327)
    - 1951 (Box 266, Folder 6328-6343)
    - 1950 (Box 266, Folder 6344-6345)
    - 1952 (Box 267, Folder 6346-6362)
    - 1954 (Box 268, Folder 6363-6372)
    - 1953 (Box 268, Folder 6373-6379)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 269, Folder 6380)
    - 1953 (Box 269, Folder 6381-6389)
    - 1955 (Box 269, Folder 6390-6402)
    - 1956 (Box 270, Folder 6403-6422)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 271, Folder 6423)
    - 1959 (Box 271, Folder 6424-6425)
    - 1957-1959 (Box 271, Folder 6426)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 271, Folder 6427)
    - 1958 (Box 271, Folder 6428-6429)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 271, Folder 6430)
    - 1957 (Box 271, Folder 6431-6438)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 271, Folder 6439)
    - 1956 (Box 271, Folder 6440)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 271, Folder 6441)
    - 1954 (Box 271, Folder 6442)
    - 1957 (Box 272, Folder 6443-6462)
    - 1958 (Box 273, Folder 6463-6477)
    - 1959 (Box 273, Folder 6478-6480)
    - 1959 (continued) (Box 274, Folder 6481-6487)
    - 1959: Grand Coulee Dam (Box 274, Folder 6488)
    - 1959 (Box 274, Folder 6489)
    - 1957: Columbia Basin Project (Box 274, Folder 6490)
    - 1959: Columbia Basin Project (Box 274, Folder 6491)
    - 1959 (Box 274, Folder 6492-6498)
    - 1957-1959 (Box 274, Folder 6499-6500)
    - 1959: Chief Joseph Dam Project (Box 274, Folder 6501)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 274, Folder 6502)
    - 1955 (Box 275, Folder 6503)
    - 1954: Alameda (Box 275, Folder 6504)
    - 1959: Reclamation in the West (Box 275, Folder 6505)
    - 1959: House Resolutions (Box 275, Folder 6506)
    - 1957: House Resolutions (Box 275, Folder 6507)
    - 1961: National Water Resources (Box 275, Folder 6508)
    - 1957: Water Storage Bill (Box 275, Folder 6509)
    - 1959: H.R. 3312 (Box 275, Folder 6510)
    - 1959: Dam Legislation (Box 275, Folder 6511)
    - 1956-1958: Alameda (Box 275, Folder 6512)
    - 1955-1959: Methow (Box 275, Folder 6513)
    - 1955: Grand Coulee Dam (Box 275, Folder 6514)
    - 1955: Dams (Box 275, Folder 6515)
    - 1955: Lake Chelan Reclamation (Box 275, Folder 6516)
    - 1961: Reclamation (Box 275, Folder 6517)
    - 1961: Lake Roosevelt (Box 275, Folder 6518)
    - 1961: Columbia/Lower Willamette Rivers (Box 275, Folder 6519)
    - 1961: Program of the Bureau of Reclamation in the Pacific NW (Box 275, Folder 6520)
    - 1961: Columbia, Lower Willamette Rivers (Box 275, Folder 6521)
    - 1961 (Box 275, Folder 6522)
    - 1961: Stehekin Debris Removal (Box 275, Folder 6523)
    - 1961: Bead Lake (Box 275, Folder 6524)
    - 1961: Columbia Basin Project (Box 276, Folder 6525)
    - 1961: Lower Monumental Snake River (Box 276, Folder 6526)
    - 1961 (Box 276, Folder 6527-6528)
    - 1961: Bureau of Reclamation (Box 276, Folder 6529)
    - 1960: Columbia Basin (Box 276, Folder 6530)
    - 1960: "Water Wealth" (Box 276, Folder 6531)
    - 1960 (Box 276, Folder 6532-6534)
    - 1960: Chief Joseph Dam (Box 276, Folder 6535)
    - 1960: Water and Soil Conservation (Box 276, Folder 6536)
    - 1960: Columbia Basin Project (Box 276, Folder 6537)
    - 1960: Water Pollution Control (Box 276, Folder 6538)
    - 1960: Columbia Basin Project (Box 276, Folder 6539)
    - 1960: Columbia River Basin (Box 276, Folder 6540)
    - 1962: The Columbia Interstate Compact (Box 277, Folder 6541)
    - 1962: Reclamation: Whitestone, Coulee, Ice Harbor (Box 277, Folder 6542)
    - 1962: Reclamation Water Resource Development (Box 277, Folder 6543)
    - 1962: Reclamation Water and Lake Chelan (Box 277, Folder 6544)
    - 1962 (Box 277, Folder 6545)
    - 1962: Mann Creek (Box 277, Folder 6546)
    - 1962: Reclamation NW Rivers and Dams (Box 277, Folder 6547)
    - 1962: Columbia Basin Project (Box 277, Folder 6548)
    - 1962: Reclamation: Land Acquisitions (Box 277, Folder 6549)
    - 1962: Water Resource Commission and Mann Creek (Box 277, Folder 6550)
    - 1962: Rivers and Power (Box 277, Folder 6551)
  - Irrigation and reclamation: Spokane Valley
    - 1962 (Box 277, Folder 6552-6555)
    - 1961: H.R. 7407 (Box 277, Folder 6556)
    - 1961 (Box 277, Folder 6557)
    - 1962 (Box 277, Folder 6558)
    - 1961: Reappraisal (Box 277, Folder 6559-6560)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 277, Folder 6561)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 277, Folder 6562)
    - 1959 (Box 277, Folder 6563-6564)
    - 1959 (continued) (Box 278, Folder 6565-6567)
    - 1958 (Box 278, Folder 6568-6569)
    - 1957 (Box 278, Folder 6570-6572)
    - 1956 (Box 278, Folder 6573-6574)
    - 1955 (Box 278, Folder 6575)
    - 1954 (Box 278, Folder 6576-6577)
    - 1954: Reconnaissance Report (Box 278, Folder 6578)
  - Irrigation and Reclamation
    - 1964: Water Resources Research Institute (Box 278, Folder 6579)
    - 1964: Reclamation (Box 278, Folder 6580)
    - 1964: Reclamation/Water Resources (Box 278, Folder 6581)
    - 1964: Land and Water Conservation Fund (Box 278, Folder 6582)
    - 1964: Land and Water Conservation Fund (Box 279, Folder 6583)
    - 1964: Reclamation (Box 279, Folder 6584)
    - 1964: Land and Water Conservation Fund Act (Box 279, Folder 6585)
    - 1964: Reclamation (Box 279, Folder 6586)
    - 1964: Banks Lake (Box 279, Folder 6587)
    - 1964: Program of the Bureau of Reclamation (Box 279, Folder 6588)
    - 1963-1964: Reclamation Budget (Box 279, Folder 6589)
    - 1963-1964: Bridge Proposals (Box 279, Folder 6590)
    - 1963: Water Resources (Box 279, Folder 6591)
    - 1963: Reclamation Miscellaneous (Box 279, Folder 6592)
    - 1963: Reclamation Miscellaneous (Box 279, Folder 6593)
    - 1963: Lake Roosevelt (Box 279, Folder 6594)
    - 1963: Reclamation (Box 279, Folder 6595)
    - 1963: Reclamation: Lake Chelan Area (Box 279, Folder 6596)
    - 1963: Reclamation: Water Levels Banks Lake and Lake Roosevelt (Box 279, Folder 6597)
    - 1963: Reclamation: Lake Roosevelt (Box 279, Folder 6598)